<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Javascript on Matt Snider</title>
    <link>https://matt-snider.github.io/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Javascript on Matt Snider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>© 2020 Matt Snider</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://matt-snider.github.io/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AngularJS Bootstrap</title>
      <link>https://matt-snider.github.io/projects/angularjs-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt-snider.github.io/projects/angularjs-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a now abandoned attempt at building a Bootstrap4-based component framework for AngularJS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time, the company where I worked used AngularJS and Bootstrap, but decided against several existing component frameworks for various reasons. I decided it would be fun (and maybe even useful!) to build one myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vue Guitar Chords</title>
      <link>https://matt-snider.github.io/projects/vue-guitar-chords/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt-snider.github.io/projects/vue-guitar-chords/</guid>
      <description>This was a fun one to learn more about VueJS. I play guitar (or used to at least&amp;hellip;) and thought it would be cool to build chord diagrams and an editor for them.
Here what the chord diagrams look like:
  Other than those basic features I haven&amp;rsquo;t really worked on it much and don&amp;rsquo;t have plans to.
There is also a basic demo here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh City Farms</title>
      <link>https://matt-snider.github.io/work/fresh-city-farms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt-snider.github.io/work/fresh-city-farms/</guid>
      <description> Development of new features and maintenance of existing code for Toronto-based eCommerce platform Ongoing frontend modernization &amp;amp; migration from jQuery to VueJS  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surf Media Gmbh</title>
      <link>https://matt-snider.github.io/work/surf-media-gmbh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matt-snider.github.io/work/surf-media-gmbh/</guid>
      <description> Designed, implemented and tested web services for an advertising performance network in a Deis-based microservices architecture REST APIs and message consumers using Java/Dropwizard and Python/Flask/DRF AngularJS-based frontend Developed a SOCKS5 proxy server to interface with devices as part of our automated ad-testing infrastructure Mentored more junior coworkers through pair programming &amp;amp; code reviews  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>